Guide to the Pittsburgh Zionist District Records, 1945-1965 AIS.1968.12
ULS Archives & Special Collections
- Regional Reports: Erie, 1957-1958 (Box 27, Folder 10)
- Regional Reports: Farrell, 1957-1958 (Box 27, Folder 11)
- Regional Reports: Indiana, 1957-1958 (Box 27, Folder 12)
- Regional Reports: Greensburg, 1957-1958 (Box 27, Folder 13)
- Regional Reports: Jeannette, 1957-1958 (Box 27, Folder 14)
- Regional Reports:Johnstown, 1957-1958 (Box 27, Folder 15)
- Regional Reports: Kittanning, 1957-1958 (Box 27, Folder 16)
- Regional Reports: Latrobe, 1957-1958 (Box 27, Folder 17)
- Regional Reports: McKeesport, 1957-1958 (Box 27, Folder 18-19)
- Regional Reports: Mon Valley, 1957-1958 (Box 27, Folder 20)
- Regional Reports: New Castle, 1957-1958 (Box 27, Folder 21)
- Regional Reports: New Kensington, 1957-1958 (Box 27, Folder 22)
- Regional Reports: Oil City, 1957-1958 (Box 27, Folder 23)
- Regional Reports: Sharon, 1957-1958 (Box 27, Folder 24)
- Regional Reports: Uniontown, 1957-1958 (Box 27, Folder 25)
- Regional Reports: Vandergrift, 1957-1958 (Box 27, Folder 26)
- Regional Reports: Warren, PA, 1957-1958 (Box 27, Folder 27)
- Regional Reports: Warren, OH, 1957-1958 (Box 27, Folder 28)
- Regional Reports: Washington, 1957-1958 (Box 27, Folder 29)
- Regional Reports: Wheeling, 1957-1958 (Box 27, Folder 30)
- Regional Reports: Youngstown, 1957-1958 (Box 27, Folder 31)
- AZF Region, 1957-1958 (Box 28, Folder 1)
- Board, 1957-1958 (Box 28, Folder 2)
- Budget and Finance, 1957-1958 (Box 28, Folder 3)
- Kfar Silver ZOA House, 1957-1958 (Box 28, Folder 4)
- Executive Committee, 1957-1958 (Box 28, Folder 5)
- Membership Reports, 1957-1958 (Box 28, Folder 6)
- List of All Mailings Region, 1957-1958 (Box 28, Folder 7)
- H.H. Kimel, 1957-1958 (Box 28, Folder 8)
- Samuel Saul, Jr., 1957-1958 (Box 28, Folder 9)
- ZOA House, 1957-1958 (Box 28, Folder 10)
- David Lowenthal, 1957-1958 (Box 28, Folder 11)
- Sam Saul Dinner, May 5, 1957 (Box 28, Folder 12)
- AZF Program Book, 1957-1958 (Box 29, Folder 1)
- AZF Income, 1957-1958 (Box 29, Folder 2)
- AZF Data, 1957-1958 (Box 29, Folder 3)
- American Zionist Committee for Public Affairs, 1957-1958 (Box 29, Folder 4)
- American Zionist Council, 1957-1958 (Box 29, Folder 5)
- ZOA House, 1957-1958 (Box 29, Folder 6)
- Relations With and Reports from World and National Organizations, 1957-1958 (Box 29, Folder 7)
- N.Y. Releases, 1957-1958 (Box 29, Folder 8)
- ZOA- Officers 2nd NEC, 1957-1958 (Box 29, Folder 9)
- Political Reviews, 1957-1958 (Box 29, Folder 10)
- Political Developments, 1957-1958 (Box 29, Folder 11)
- Near East Report, 1957-1958 (Box 29, Folder 12)
- Israel Information, 1957-1958 (Box 30, Folder 1)
- Education, 1957-1958 (Box 30, Folder 2)
- Books, 1957-1958 (Box 30, Folder 3-4)
- Young Zionist District Correspondence, 1957-1958 (Box 30, Folder 5)
- Youth Commission Correspondence, 1957-1958 (Box 30, Folder 6)
- Youth Commission, 1957-1958 (Box 30, Folder 7)
- Young Zionist District, 1957-1958 (Box 30, Folder 8)
- Congratulations, 1957-1958 (Box 30, Folder 9)
- Condolences and Recovery, 1957-1958 (Box 30, Folder 10)
- AZF Miscellaneous, 1957-1958 (Box 30, Folder 11)
- AZF Photos, 1957-1958 (Box 30, Folder 12)
- Dr. Sindey A. Marks Correspondence, 1958-1959 (Box 31, Folder 1-2)
- AZF Correspondence, 1958-1959 (Box 31, Folder 3)
- Dr. Morris A. Landes, 1958-1959 (Box 31, Folder 4)
- Miscellaneous Correspondence, 1958-1959 (Box 31, Folder 5)
- H.H. Kimel, 1958-1959 (Box 31, Folder 6-7)
- A. Flitman, 1958-1959 (Box 31, Folder 8)
- Leon Ilutovich, 1958-1959 (Box 31, Folder 9)
- Irwin Stahl, 1958-1959 (Box 31, Folder 10)
- Board Pending, 1958-1959 (Box 31, Folder 11)
- Board Minutes and Agendas, 1958-1959 (Box 31, Folder 12)
- Executive Committee Region Officers, 1958-1959 (Box 31, Folder 13)
- Board of Directors, 1958-1959 (Box 31, Folder 14)
- Executive Committee Attendance Sheet, 1958-1959 (Box 31, Folder 15)
- Board of Directors Meeting Attendance, 1958-1959 (Box 31, Folder 16)
- Executive Committee Agendas, 1958-1959 (Box 31, Folder 17)
- Executive Committee, 1958-1959 (Box 31, Folder 18)
- Executive Committee Minutes, 1958-1959 (Box 31, Folder 19)
- Board Correspondence, 1958-1959 (Box 31, Folder 20)
- Program Committee, 1958-1959 (Box 32, Folder 1)
- Program Data, 1958-1959 (Box 32, Folder 2)
- Program Correspondence, 1958-1959 (Box 32, Folder 3)
- Nominations Committee, 1958-1959 (Box 32, Folder 4)
- Cultural Committee, 1958-1959 (Box 32, Folder 5)
- Membership Correspondence, 1958-1959 (Box 32, Folder 6-7)
- AZF Mailings to Workers, 1958-1959 (Box 32, Folder 8)
- Membership Mailings to Workers, 1958-1959 (Box 32, Folder 9)
- Membership Billings, 1958-1959 (Box 32, Folder 10)
- Membership Lists, 1958-1959 (Box 32, Folder 10)
- Membership Lists, 1958-1959 (Box 33, Folder 1)
- Membership Reports, 1958-1959 (Box 33, Folder 2)
- Advance and Duplicate Dues, 1958-1959 (Box 33, Folder 3)
- Membership Data, 1958-1959 (Box 33, Folder 4)
- Membership Kickoff, 1958-1959 (Box 33, Folder 5)
- Membership Campaigns, 1958-1959 (Box 33, Folder 6-7)
- Membership Campaign Victory Dinner, April 20, 1959 (Box 33, Folder 8)
- Membership Campaign Reports of Meetings, 1958-1959 (Box 33, Folder 9)
- Membership Campaign Planning- Photos, 1958-1959 (Box 33, Folder 10)
- Revolving Fund, 1958-1959 (Box 33, Folder 11)
- Membership Campaigns, 1958-1959 (Box 33, Folder 12-13)
- Journal Ads, 1958-1959 (Box 34, Folder 1)
- General, 1958-1959 (Box 34, Folder 2)
- Financial Report, 1958-1959 (Box 34, Folder 3)
- Tax Receipts, 1958-1959 (Box 34, Folder 4)
- Financial Reports, 1958-1959 (Box 34, Folder 5)
- Budget, 1958-1959 (Box 34, Folder 6)
- Bond- Loans, 1958-1959 (Box 34, Folder 7)
- Paid Bills- April, May, June, 1958 (Box 34, Folder 8)
- Paid Bills- January, February, March, 1959 (Box 34, Folder 9)
- Paid Bills- July, August, September, 1959 (Box 34, Folder 10)
- Paid Bills- October, November, December, 1959 (Box 34, Folder 11)
- Paid Bills- October, November, December, 1960 (Box 34, Folder 12)
- Paid Bills- January, February, March, 1958 (Box 34, Folder 13)
- Paid Bills, 1958-1959 (Box 35, Folder 1)
- Palestine Economic Corp, 1958-1959 (Box 35, Folder 2)
- United Jewish Federation, 1958-1959 (Box 35, Folder 3)
- Membership Mailings by Workers, 1958-1959 (Box 35, Folder 4)
- United Jewish Federation, 1958-1959 (Box 35, Folder 5)
- American Zionist Fund Unpaid Pledges, 1958-1959 (Box 35, Folder 6)
- Fund Drives, 1958-1959 (Box 35, Folder 7)
- Bond Loans to Zionist Organization of America, 1958-1959 (Box 35, Folder 8)
- Bonds, 1958-1959 (Box 35, Folder 9)
- American Zionist Fund Program Book, 1958-1959 (Box 35, Folder 10)
- Jewish National Fund, 1958-1959 (Box 35, Folder 11)
- Fund Drives, 1958-1959 (Box 35, Folder 12-13)
- Conferences, 1958-1959 (Box 36, Folder 1)
- N.E.C.-P.G.I.A. March 21-25, 1959 (Box 36, Folder 2)
- Convention- National, 1958-1959 (Box 36, Folder 3)
- Convention, 1958-1959 (Box 36, Folder 4-5)
- ZOA Convention, 1958-1959 (Box 36, Folder 6)
- Convention, 1958-1959 (Box 36, Folder 7-8)
- Convention Releases, 1958-1959 (Box 37, Folder 1)
- Convention, H. Kimel, 1958-1959 (Box 37, Folder 2)
- ZOA Convention Releases, 1958-1959 (Box 37, Folder 3-4)
- Purim Dance, 1958-1959 (Box 38, Folder 1-2)
- Social, 1958-1959 (Box 38, Folder 3)
- Israel Tours, 1958-1959 (Box 38, Folder 4)
- Seating- AZF, 1958-1959 (Box 38, Folder 5)
- AZF Seating, 1958-1959 (Box 38, Folder 6-7)
- AZF Kickoff, 1958-1959 (Box 38, Folder 8)
- Program Meeting, Symposium- Foster Hall, Jan. 28, 1959 (Box 38, Folder 9)
- Speakers, 1958-1959 (Box 38, Folder 10)
- Club Program Service, 1958-1959 (Box 38, Folder 11)
- Music Festival, 1958-1959 (Box 38, Folder 12)
- Holidays Information, 1958-1959 (Box 38, Folder 13)
- Publicity, 1958-1959 (Box 39, Folder 1)
- Interfaith, 1958-1959 (Box 39, Folder 2)
- Harold P. Manson, Dept. of Public Information, 1958-1959 (Box 39, Folder 3)
- Organizations Lists, 1958-1959 (Box 39, Folder 4)
- Zionist Council Correspondence, 1958-1959 (Box 39, Folder 5)
- Zionist Council- Anniversary Program, 1958-1959 (Box 39, Folder 6)
- Public Relations, General, 1958-1959 (Box 39, Folder 7)
- Harold P. Manson, Dept. of Public Information, 1958-1959 (Box 39, Folder 8)
- Zionist Congress, 1958-1959 (Box 39, Folder 9)
- N.Y. Releases, 1958-1959 (Box 39, Folder 10)
- AZF Data, 1958-1959 (Box 39, Folder 11)
- American Zionist Council, 1958-1959 (Box 39, Folder 12)
- AZF Income, 1958-1959 (Box 39, Folder 13)
- Hebrew University, 1958-1959 (Box 40, Folder 1)
- Hebrew Lessons, 1958-1959 (Box 40, Folder 2)
- Kfar Silver, 1958-1959 (Box 40, Folder 3)
- Books, 1958-1959 (Box 40, Folder 4)
- Education, 1958-1959 (Box 40, Folder 5)
- Zionist Literature, 1958-1959 (Box 40, Folder 6)
- Kibbutz Life Facts and Figures, 1958-1959 (Box 40, Folder 7)
- Youth Commission, 1958-1959 (Box 40, Folder 8)
- Youth Commission Region, 1958-1959 (Box 40, Folder 9)
- Young Zionist District, 1958-1959 (Box 40, Folder 10)
- Youth Commission Data, Mr. Hy Kimel, 1958-1959 (Box 40, Folder 11)
- Youth Commission- Survey Committee, 1958-1959 (Box 40, Folder 12)
- Youth Commission, 1958-1959 (Box 41, Folder 1)
- Congratulations, 1958-1959 (Box 41, Folder 2)
- Condolences and Recovery, 1958-1959 (Box 41, Folder 3)
- Office Equipment, 1958-1959 (Box 41, Folder 4)
- Changes of Address, 1958-1959 (Box 41, Folder 5)
- AZF Photos, 1958-1959 (Box 41, Folder 6)
- Signatures, 1958-1959 (Box 41, Folder 7)
- ZOA House, 1958-1959 (Box 41, Folder 8)
- C. Joseph Recht, 1958-1959 (Box 42, Folder 1)
- Executive Council, 1958-1959 (Box 42, Folder 2)
- Tri-State Zionist Region, Officers, 1958-1959 (Box 42, Folder 3)
- Key Leaders, 1958-1959 (Box 42, Folder 4)
- Bills Payable, Region, 1958-1959 (Box 42, Folder 5)
- Life Members, 1958-1959 (Box 42, Folder 6)
- AZF Lists, 1958-1959 (Box 42, Folder 7)
- American Zionist Committee for Public Affairs, 1958-1959 (Box 42, Folder 8)
- Annual Meeting, 1958-1959 (Box 42, Folder 9)
- AZF Mailings to Prospects, 1958-1959 (Box 42, Folder 10)
- AZF Miscellaneous, 1958-1959 (Box 42, Folder 11)
- Membership Correspondence, 1958-1959 (Box 42, Folder 12)
- Membership Annual Statistics, 1958-1959 (Box 42, Folder 13)
- Minutes, 1958-1959 (Box 42, Folder 14)
- Membership Roll Call, 1958-1959 (Box 42, Folder 15)
- Nominations Committee, 1958-1959 (Box 42, Folder 16)
- Officers, 1958-1959 (Box 42, Folder 17-18)
- Regional Leadership, 1958-1959 (Box 42, Folder 19)
- Regional, 1958-1959 (Box 42, Folder 20)
- Regional Conference, June 7, 1959 (Box 43, Folder 1)
- Photos Region, 1958-1959 (Box 43, Folder 2)
- Region Conference, 1958-1959 (Box 43, Folder 3)
- Membership Correspondence Region, 1958-1959 (Box 43, Folder 4)
- ZOA House, 1958-1959 (Box 43, Folder 5)
- Nominations Committee, Region, 1958-1959 (Box 43, Folder 6)
- C.J. Recht, 1958-1959 (Box 43, Folder 7)
- Akron, Ohio, 1958-1959 (Box 44, Folder 1)
- Charleston, W.Va., 1958-1959 (Box 44, Folder 2)
- Aliquippa, 1958-1959 (Box 44, Folder 3)
- Altoona, 1958-1959 (Box 44, Folder 4)
- Beaver Falls, 1958-1959 (Box 44, Folder 5)
- Brownsville, 1958-1959 (Box 44, Folder 6)
- Butler, 1958-1959 (Box 44, Folder 7)
- Canonsburg, 1958-1959 (Box 44, Folder 8)
- Canton, Ohio, 1958-1959 (Box 44, Folder 9)
- Charleston, W.Va., 1958-1959 (Box 44, Folder 10)
- East Liverpool, Ohio, 1958-1959 (Box 44, Folder 11)
- Erie, 1958-1959 (Box 44, Folder 12)
- Farrell, 1958-1959 (Box 44, Folder 13)
- Greensburg, 1958-1959 (Box 44, Folder 14)
- Indiana, 1958-1959 (Box 44, Folder 15)
- Jeannette, 1958-1959 (Box 44, Folder 16)
- Johnstown, 1958-1959 (Box 44, Folder 17)
- Kittanning, 1958-1959 (Box 44, Folder 18)
- Latrobe, 1958-1959 (Box 44, Folder 19)
- McKeesport, 1958-1959 (Box 44, Folder 20)
- Mon Valley, 1958-1959 (Box 44, Folder 21)
- New Castle and Ellwood, 1958-1959 (Box 44, Folder 22)
- Oil City, 1958-1959 (Box 44, Folder 23)
- Sharon, 1958-1959 (Box 44, Folder 24)
- Steubenville, Ohio, 1958-1959 (Box 44, Folder 25)
- Uniontown, 1958-1959 (Box 44, Folder 26)
- Vandergrift, 1958-1959 (Box 44, Folder 27)
- Warren, Ohio, 1958-1959 (Box 44, Folder 28)
- Warren, PA, 1958-1959 (Box 44, Folder 29)
- Wheeling, W.Va., 1958-1959 (Box 44, Folder 30)
- Youngstown, Ohio, 1958-1959 (Box 44, Folder 31)
- Inquiries, 1959-1960 (Box 45, Folder 1)
- Leon Ilutovich Correspondence, 1959-1960 (Box 45, Folder 2)
- Dr. Sidney A. Marks Correspondence, 1959-1960 (Box 45, Folder 3)
- Dr. Morris A. Landes, 1959-1960 (Box 45, Folder 4)
- Lyndon Johnson, 1959-1960 (Box 45, Folder 5)
- AZF Correspondence, 1959-1960 (Box 45, Folder 6)
- H.H. Kimel, 1959-1960 (Box 45, Folder 7)
- Board of Directors, Minutes and Agendas, 1959-1960 (Box 45, Folder 8)
- B'nai Israel, Board Annual Dinner, June 14, 1960 (Box 45, Folder 9)
- Pittsburgh Zionist District, Officer, Directors, Executive Comm., 1959-1960 (Box 45, Folder 10)
- Board Dinner, June 30, 1959 (Box 45, Folder 11)
- Board of Directors Attendance Record, 1959-1960 (Box 45, Folder 12)
- Executive Committee Lists, 1959-1960 (Box 45, Folder 13)
- Board Pending, 1959-1960 (Box 45, Folder 14)
- Executive Board Minutes (See Box 31), 1959-1960 (Box 45, Folder 15)
- Zionist Council Lists, 1959-1960 (Box 45, Folder 16)
- Pittsburgh Zionist District Officers, Board of Directors, Executive Committee, 1959-1960 (Box 45, Folder 17)
- Board of Directors, 1959-1960 (Box 45, Folder 18)
- Executive Committee Agendas and Correspondence, 1959-1960 (Box 46, Folder 1)
- Zionist Council, Minutes, Lists, Correspondence, 1959-1960 (Box 46, Folder 2-3)
- Board Correspondence, Notice of Meetings, 1959-1960 (Box 46, Folder 4)
- Miscellaneous Correspondence, 1959-1960 (Box 46, Folder 5)
- Council Correspondence, 1959-1960 (Box 46, Folder 6)
- Zionist Council Correspondence, 1959-1960 (Box 46, Folder 7)
- A. Flitman, 1959-1960 (Box 46, Folder 8)
- Nominations Committee, 1959-1960 (Box 46, Folder 9)
- Kfar Silver, 1959-1960 (Box 46, Folder 10)
- Membership Study Committee, M. Holstein, 1959-1960 (Box 46, Folder 11)
- Program Committee, 1959-1960 (Box 46, Folder 12)
- Shekel Campaign, 1959-1960 (Box 46, Folder 13)
- ZOA House, 1959-1960 (Box 46, Folder 14)
- Cultural Committee, 1959-1960 (Box 46, Folder 15)
- Membership Study Committee, 1959-1960 (Box 46, Folder 16)
- Program Meetings- Symposium- Foster Hall, 1959-1960 (Box 46, Folder 17)
- Membership Correspondence, 1959-1960 (Box 47, Folder 1)
- Membership Mailing by Workers, 1959-1960 (Box 47, Folder 2)
- AZF Data, 1959-1960 (Box 47, Folder 3)
- AZF to Prospects, 1959-1960 (Box 47, Folder 4)
- AZP Mailings to Workers, 1959-1960 (Box 47, Folder 5)
- Membership Statistics and Analysis, 1959-1960 (Box 47, Folder 6)
- Membership Billings, 1959-1960 (Box 47, Folder 7)
- Membership Data, 1959-1960 (Box 47, Folder 8)
- Membership Reports, 1959-1960 (Box 47, Folder 9)
- Membership Planning, 1959-1960 (Box 47, Folder 10)
- Membership Kickoff, 1959-1960 (Box 47, Folder 11)
- Campaign Comments, 1959-1960 (Box 47, Folder 12)
- Membership Mailings to Workers, 1959-1960 (Box 48, Folder 1)
- Membership Camp Victory Dinner, April 27, 1960 (Box 48, Folder 2)
- Membership Report Meetings, 1959-1960 (Box 48, Folder 3)
- Membership Lists, Workers, Cards Assigned, 1959-1960 (Box 48, Folder 4)
- Membership Prospect Lists, 1959-1960 (Box 48, Folder 5)
- Financial Reports, 1959-1960 (Box 48, Folder 6)
- Financial Statements, October 1 - September 30, 1959-1960 (Box 48, Folder 7)
- Tax Receipts, 1959-1960 (Box 48, Folder 8)
- Advance and Duplicate Dues, 1959-1960 (Box 48, Folder 9)
- Budget, 1959-1960 (Box 48, Folder 10)
- Lease (308 MaGee), 1959-1960 (Box 48, Folder 11)
- International Revenue- ZOA Deductions, 1959-1960 (Box 48, Folder 12)
- AZF Income, 1959-1960 (Box 48, Folder 13)
- Paid Bills- January, February, March, 1960 (Box 48, Folder 14)
- ZOA Convention, Washington D.C. Kit Contents- September 10-13, 1959 (Box 49, Folder 1)
- Paid Bills- April, May, June, 1960 (Box 49, Folder 2)
- Paid Bills- July, August, September, 1960 (Box 49, Folder 3)
- United Jewish Federation, 1959-1960 (Box 49, Folder 4)
- Jewish National Fund, 1959-1960 (Box 49, Folder 5)
- Bonds, 1959-1960 (Box 49, Folder 6)
- AZF Unpaid Pledges, 1959-1960 (Box 49, Folder 7)
- AZF Prospect Lists, 1959-1960 (Box 49, Folder 8)
- AZF Lists, 1959-1960 (Box 49, Folder 9)
- AZF Prospect Lists, 1959-1960 (Box 49, Folder 10)
- Lists, 1959-1960 (Box 49, Folder 11)
- Orientation Conference, March 20, 1960 (Box 50, Folder 1)
- Program Data, Orientation Conference, March 20, 1960 (Box 50, Folder 2)
- Films, 1959-1960 (Box 50, Folder 3-4)
- Convention Releases, September 10-13, 1959 (Box 50, Folder 5)
- National Convention Lists, Delegates, 1959-1960 (Box 50, Folder 6)
- Correspondence- ZOA Convention, 1959-1960 (Box 50, Folder 7)
- Convention Mailings, Releases, August 25, 1960 (Box 50, Folder 8)
- Annual Meeting, 1959-1960 (Box 50, Folder 9)
- Israel Anniversary, May 13, 1959 (Box 51, Folder 1)
- Purim Dance, 1959-1960 (Box 51, Folder 2-3)
- Israel Tours, 1959-1960 (Box 51, Folder 4)
- Israel Tours Brochures, 1959-1960 (Box 51, Folder 5)
- Israel Information, 1959-1960 (Box 51, Folder 6)
- AZF Dinner, November 1, 1959 (Box 51, Folder 7)
- AZF Kickoff, 1959-1960 (Box 51, Folder 8)
- AZF Program Book, 1959-1960 (Box 51, Folder 9)
- Seating Charts, 1959-1960 (Box 51, Folder 10)
- Purim Dance, 1959-1960 (Box 51, Folder 11)
- Song Book, 1959-1960 (Box 52, Folder 1)
- Program Correspondence, 1959-1960 (Box 52, Folder 2)
- Program Data, 1959-1960 (Box 52, Folder 3)
- Program Data, Music Festival, February 24, 1960 (Box 52, Folder 4)
- Israel Anniversary, 1959-1960 (Box 52, Folder 5)
- Hebrew Language and Culture Departments, 1959-1960 (Box 52, Folder 6)
- Aliyah and Tours, 1959-1960 (Box 52, Folder 7)
- Zionist Council Releases, 1959-1960 (Box 52, Folder 8)
- Mayors Proclamation, April 29, 1960 (Box 52, Folder 9)
- Publicity, 1959-1960 (Box 52, Folder 10)
- Interfaith, 1959-1960 (Box 52, Folder 11)
- Pittsburgh Zionist District Officers, Board of Directors, Executive Committee, 1959-1960 (Box 52, Folder 12)
- Akron, 1959-1960 (Box 52, Folder 13)
- Altoona, 1959-1960 (Box 52, Folder 14)
- Beaver Falls, 1959-1960 (Box 52, Folder 15)
- Brownsville, 1959-1960 (Box 52, Folder 16)
- Butler, 1959-1960 (Box 52, Folder 17)
- Canton, 1959-1960 (Box 52, Folder 18)
- Charleston, 1959-1960 (Box 53, Folder 1)
- East Liverpool, 1959-1960 (Box 53, Folder 2)
- Erie, 1959-1960 (Box 53, Folder 3)
- Farrell, 1959-1960 (Box 53, Folder 4)
- Huntington, W.Va., 1959-1960 (Box 53, Folder 5)
- Indiana, 1959-1960 (Box 53, Folder 6)
- Greensburg, 1959-1960 (Box 53, Folder 7)
- Johnstown, 1959-1960 (Box 53, Folder 8)
- New Kensington, 1959-1960 (Box 53, Folder 9)
- New Castle, 1959-1960 (Box 53, Folder 10)
- Sharon, 1959-1960 (Box 53, Folder 11)
- Steubenville, 1959-1960 (Box 53, Folder 12)
- Uniontown, 1959-1960 (Box 53, Folder 13)
- Warren, Ohio, 1959-1960 (Box 53, Folder 14)
- Washington, 1959-1960 (Box 53, Folder 15-16)
- Wheeling, 1959-1960 (Box 53, Folder 17)
- Youngstown, Ohio, 1959-1960 (Box 53, Folder 18)
- Other Regions- Releases, 1959-1960 (Box 54, Folder 1)
- NEC and National Officers, 1959-1960 (Box 54, Folder 2)
- New York Releases, 1959-1960 (Box 54, Folder 3)
- American Zion Committee for Public Affairs, 1959-1960 (Box 54, Folder 4)
- American Zionist Council, 1959-1960 (Box 54, Folder 5)
- Israel Anniversary, 1959-1960 (Box 54, Folder 6)
- Refugee Year, 1959-1960 (Box 54, Folder 7)
- Political Development, 1959-1960 (Box 54, Folder 8)
- Bulletin, 1959-1960 (Box 54, Folder 9)
- American-Israel Society, 1959-1960 (Box 54, Folder 10)
- Zionist Ideology Articles, 1959-1960 (Box 54, Folder 11)
- Herzliah Hebrew Teachers Institute, 1959-1960 (Box 54, Folder 12)
- Library Committee, 1959-1960 (Box 54, Folder 13)
- Hebrew at Home, T.V. Lessons, 1959-1960 (Box 54, Folder 14)
- Hebrew Day School, 1959-1960 (Box 54, Folder 15)
- Books, 1959-1960 (Box 54, Folder 16)
- Youth Commission, 1959-1960 (Box 54, Folder 17)
- Youth and Young Zionist, 1959-1960 (Box 54, Folder 18)
- Changes of Address, 1959-1960 (Box 54, Folder 19)
- Condolences and Recovery, 1959-1960 (Box 54, Folder 20)
- Congratulations, 1959-1960 (Box 54, Folder 21)
- Cuts, 1959-1960 (Box 54, Folder 22)
- Photos, 1959-1960 (Box 54, Folder 23-24)
- Executive Director Correspondence, 1960-1961 (Box 55, Folder 1)
- Irwin Stahl Correspondence, 1960-1961 (Box 55, Folder 2)
- Leon Ilutovitch Correspondence, 1960-1961 (Box 55, Folder 3)
- AZF Correspondence, 1960-1961 (Box 55, Folder 4)
- J.B. Bernstein, 1960-1961 (Box 55, Folder 5)
- H.H. Kimel, 1960-1961 (Box 55, Folder 6)
- Jacob Wolk Golden Book, 1960-1961 (Box 55, Folder 7)
- Executive Committee Attendance, 1960-1961 (Box 55, Folder 8)
- Board Dinner, 1960-1961 (Box 55, Folder 9)
- Board of Directors Meeting Attendance, 1960-1961 (Box 55, Folder 10)
- Executive Committee Lists, 1960-1961 (Box 55, Folder 11)
- Executive Committee Meeting, 1960-1961 (Box 55, Folder 12)
- Zionist Council, 1960-1961 (Box 55, Folder 13-14)
- Zionist Council Pittsburgh, 1960-1961 (Box 55, Folder 15)
- Miscellaneous Correspondence, 1960-1961 (Box 55, Folder 16)
- Board Pending, 1960-1961 (Box 55, Folder 17)
- Executive Committee Meetings Agendas, Minutes, Correspondence, 1960-1961 (Box 56, Folder 1)
- Executive Committee Attendance, 1960-1961 (Box 56, Folder 2)
- Executive Committee Agendas and Correspondence, 1960-1961 (Box 56, Folder 3)
- Board Minutes and Agendas, 1960-1961 (Box 56, Folder 4)
- Zionist Council Anniversary Correspondence, 1960-1961 (Box 56, Folder 5)
- Board Correspondence, 1960-1961 (Box 56, Folder 6)
- Nominations Committee, 1960-1961 (Box 56, Folder 7)
- Program Committee, 1960-1961 (Box 57, Folder 1)
- Picnic Committee, 1960-1961 (Box 57, Folder 2)
- Library Committee, 1960-1961 (Box 57, Folder 3)
- Cultural Committee, 1960-1961 (Box 57, Folder 4)
- American-Israel Public Affairs Committee, 1960-1961 (Box 57, Folder 5)
- Cultural Committee, 1960-1961 (Box 57, Folder 6)
- AZF Program Book, 1960-1961 (Box 57, Folder 7)
- Membership Correspondence, 1960-1961 (Box 57, Folder 8)
- Membership "Campaign Comments", 1960-1961 (Box 57, Folder 9)
- Membership Mail to Workers, 1960-1961 (Box 57, Folder 10)
- Membership Mail by Workers, 1960-1961 (Box 57, Folder 11)
- AZF Mailings to Workers, 1960-1961 (Box 57, Folder 12)
- Lists, 1960-1961 (Box 58, Folder 1)
- Membership Reports, 1960-1961 (Box 58, Folder 2)
- Membership Statistics and Analyses, 1960-1961 (Box 58, Folder 3)
- Advance and Duplicate Dues, 1960-1961 (Box 58, Folder 4)
- Membership Prospect Lists, 1960-1961 (Box 58, Folder 5)
- Membership Campaign Closing Dinner, 1960-1961 (Box 58, Folder 6)
- Membership Campaign Structure, 1960-1961 (Box 58, Folder 7)
- Membership Campaign Reports, Meetings, Statistics, Agendas, 1960-1961 (Box 58, Folder 8)
- Membership Data, 1960-1961 (Box 58, Folder 9)
- Membership Kickoff, 1960-1961 (Box 58, Folder 10)
- Budget, 1960-1961 (Box 59, Folder 1)
- Tax Receipts, 1960-1961 (Box 59, Folder 2)
- Financial Reports, 1960-1961 (Box 59, Folder 3)
- AZF Income, 1960-1961 (Box 59, Folder 4)
- Paid Bills- January, February, March, 1961 (Box 59, Folder 5)
- Paid Bills- April, May, June, 1961 (Box 59, Folder 6)
- Paid Bills- July, August, September, 1961 (Box 59, Folder 7)
- Paid Bills- October, November, December, 1961 (Box 59, Folder 8)
- U.J.F., 1960-1961 (Box 59, Folder 9)
- Jewish National Fund, 1960-1961 (Box 59, Folder 10)
- AZF Miscellaneous, 1960-1961 (Box 59, Folder 11)
- Bonds, 1960-1961 (Box 59, Folder 12)
- AZF Mailings to Prospects, 1960-1961 (Box 59, Folder 13)
- Fund Drives, 1960-1961 (Box 60, Folder 1-2)
- Bonds, Dinner, August 18, 1960 (Box 60, Folder 3)
- AZF Unpaid, 1960-1961 (Box 60, Folder 4)
- AZF Kickoff, 1960-1961 (Box 60, Folder 5)
- Convention Releases, 1960-1961 (Box 61, Folder 1)
- National Convention, 1960-1961 (Box 61, Folder 2)
- Conventions, 1960-1961 (Box 61, Folder 3)
- Convention Releases, 1960-1961 (Box 61, Folder 4)
- Convention Kit, 1960-1961 (Box 61, Folder 5)